goantiques.com 2016-12-01

# GoAntiques

**GoAntiques Privacy Policy**

GoAntiques.com is owned and operated by Gemr, Inc. (" **GoAntiques** ," " **we** ," " **us** " or " **our(s)** "). We are committed to protecting your privacy. We have prepared this Privacy Policy to describe to you our practices regarding the Personal Information (as defined below) we collect from users (" **User(s),"** " **you** ," " **your(s)")** of the GoAntiques website, mobile application(s) and other related services (each individually or together, the "Site"). 

**By using our Site, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy and all other GoAntiques policies governing the use of the Site and you expressly consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. By using the Site you represent that you have read and understand this Privacy Policy and other GoAntiques policies and agree to be bound by the terms therein.**

Capitalized terms not defined in this Privacy Policy have the meanings given in our **Terms of Use.**

For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, "Personal Information" is any personally identifiable information about an individual person such as a person's name, physical address, email address and telephone number, and may include financial and other information provided by an individual who accesses our Site and/or uses our services. 

**TYPES OF INFORMATION WE COLLECT**

Though you may access and use portions of our Site without providing any Personal Information, in order to take advantage of the full capabilities of the Site and to obtain access to, and use of, many of the features of our Site, you must provide certain Personal Information. For example, in order to register for a membership account through the Site (each a "Membership Account"), to sell items on the Site and to request information about products and services offered on our Site you must provide certain Personal Information. 

**Personal Information Provided Voluntarily by the User.** When you register for a Membership Account you will be asked to provide Personal Information. You may also be asked to provide Personal Information when you participate in various services and offerings available through our Site, when you contact us via phone, mail, or otherwise, and when you participate in our sweepstakes, contests, surveys and related promotions. The Personal Information we may collect and store includes, but is not limited to, the following categories of information: 

● your name, mailing address, email address, telephone number, year of birth, and gender, information concerning your hobbies, interests and occupation, and financial information (for billing purposes); and community discussions, chats and correspondence. 

**Anonymous Data.** When you use our Site we may collect data that is not associated with or linked to your Personal Information (" **Anonymous Data** "). Anonymous Data does not, by itself, permit the identification of individual persons. 

**Information Collected from Other Sources.** We may obtain information about you from other sources, such as companies that update and verify email and physical addresses, for the purpose of updating and enhancing our files. 

**User Communities on our Site.** Our Site includes community areas (e.g., forums, bulletin boards and chat rooms) in which you may participate after establishing a Membership Account. Although your participation in these communities is governed by this privacy policy, there are certain important characteristics of these communities that you should always keep in mind. **** We use Membership Account registration information and other information users provide as they interact within the communities to: 

● authenticate users; provide communications from us to users regarding the community; and administer the community (including, but not limited to, managing the technical requirements of the site and monitoring submissions and posts for offensive content after posting and removing such content in our sole discretion). ****

**Please note** that information (including your name, email address, address, or phone number) you provide in a posting on community or any bulletin board is available (even after you stop participating in the community) to any other individual who has access to that same community and may be used by another individual in a manner unintended by you, including as a target for unsolicited communications. You should therefore treat any information provided by you in the content of a submission or post to a community as public information. For this reason, we urge you to act cautiously in providing any such information in your submissions or posts, as we are not liable for any use or misuse by an individual user of the information you provide in a submission or post. Upon termination of a community, Personal Information we collected through the community will continue to be treated in accordance with this privacy policy. 

**USE OF YOUR INFORMATION**

**Personal Information.** We use Personal Information you provide to us for our business purposes, such as: 

● to allow you to access your Membership Account; (ii) to confirm your identity; (iii) for marketing our products and services to you and to customize this advertising and marketing information; (iv) to contact you regarding your Membership Account and to keep records regarding your Membership Account; (v) to carry-out promotions, including but not limited to sweepstakes, contests surveys and related promotions that you have entered; (vi) to provide the services and products you request and to respond to your other requests and inquiries', (vii) to enhance our service offerings; and (viii) to adjust our Site to your personal preferences. 

**Anonymous Data.** Anonymous Data may be used to analyze request and usage patterns so that we may enhance our Site and to improve Site navigation. We reserve the right to use Anonymous Data for any purpose and disclose Anonymous Data to third parties at our sole and absolute discretion. 

**Marketing.** We do not sell or rent your Personal Information to third parties for their marketing purposes. We may aggregate and use certain non-personally identifiable information for research or marketing purposes and may share, sell and rent or trade that information and statistical data derived from such information with our marketing partners, advertisers, or other third parties for research or marketing purposes. 

**USERS OUTSIDE OF THE UNITED STATES**

The Site is available worldwide and may be operated from various locations both within and outside the United States of America ("USA"). If you are accessing and using the Site from outside the USA, please note the information that you provide may be transferred to the USA or other countries which may not provide the same level of legal data protection as the country from which you access our Site. **By using our Site and submitting information to us, you consent to such transfers and the processing of information by us as described in this privacy policy and you authorize this practice** . 

**COOKIES AND OTHER INFORMATION COLLECTED BY TECHNOLOGY**

**Cookies and Related Technology.** We use Cookies (small files placed on your hard drive) to store information about your visits to our Site and to enhance your experience when visiting our Site. For example, we use Cookies to, among other things, identify previous visitors to our Site, identify a user as he/she moves through our Site, track user visits and account set-ups, determine what set-ups are most frequently requested, and save your password so you do not have to provide it each time you visit our Site. Storing information about your visits to our Site will allow us to, on occasion, customize account pages for you. 

We do not use Cookies to collect, track, or store personally identifiable information. Our cookies will never be used to track your activity on any third party Site or to send spam. You can configure your browser to accept all Cookies, reject all Cookies, or notify you when a Cookie is received. (Each browser is different, so check the Help menu of your browser to learn how to change your Cookie preferences). You may reject, delete or otherwise disable Cookies at any time. However, by deleting, rejecting or otherwise disabling Cookies, you may interfere with your use of some of our Site or services. 

**URL Tracking.** Some of our email communications to you may include a "click-through URL" linked to a particular page on one of our Sites. By clicking on one of these URLs, you will automatically enter our Site. Our systems track this information to gauge the effectiveness of our email communications and your level of interest in particular areas. You may avoid having this information collected by avoiding clicking on URL links in our email communications. Please note, that we will NEVER send you an email with an embedded link that asks for your password or any financial or account information; passwords are for your protection. If you EVER receive such an email, please contact us immediately using the information in the section below entitled "Contact Us". 

We will use the information we automatically collected through your access and use of our Site to determine how our Site are accessed and used. For example, this information will allow us (i) to determine which pages are the most popular with users, (ii) determine if our Site are working properly, and (iii) to improve the user-experience on our Site. We do not use automatically collected information to identify a particular user. 

**BEHAVIORAL REMARKETING**

We may use third party services such as [**Google Analytics**](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/) that collect, monitor and analyze this type of information in order to increase our Service's functionality. These third party sites have separate and independent policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our Site and welcome any feedback about these sites. **** The Google Analytics remarketing service is provided by Google Inc. You can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize the Google Display Network ads by visiting [**the Google Ads Settings**](http://www.google.com/settings/ads)[1] **** page. Google also recommends installing [**the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on**](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout) [2] , which provides visitors with the ability to prevent their data from being collected from your web browser and used by Google Analytics. For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the [**Google Privacy & Terms**](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/) [3] web page. 

**THIRD PARTIES**

The Site may provide links to websites owned or operated by third parties or otherwise direct you to websites owned or operated by third parties ("Linked Site(s)"). Your use of Linked Sites will be governed by the terms of use, privacy policies and other additional terms, notices and policies set forth or referenced in those Linked Sites. . This privacy policy does not reflect the information collection, use and disclosure practices of any Linked Site or the operators or owners of Linked Sites. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these Linked Sites. To understand how a Linked Site and the owners or operators of a Linked Site will collect, use, store and otherwise make available information you should review the Linked Site's privacy policy. 

**UPDATES AND CHANGES**

GoAntiques may change this privacy policy from time to time by posting updated versions of the privacy policy here. If we make changes to the privacy policy we will post the changes on this page. Please note that information we collect will be treated in accordance with the privacy policy in effect at the time the information is collected. 

**This privacy policy was last updated in May, 2015.**

**DISCLOSURE PRACTICES**

We may share Personal Information you provide to us with certain third parties that perform services on our behalf. Those third parties may host our Site; provide certain features or functionality; print or send mailings or emails (including marketing materials); provide the services you requested, authorize and process your payments; provide customer service; analyze data; or otherwise assist us with the operation of our business. Those third parties are not authorized to use or disclose Personal Information for any purpose other than to perform the services designated by GoAntiques. We may also provide the Personal Information you provide to us to a third party if we are required by law or litigation so to disclose such Personal Information. For example, we may be required to disclose Personal Information to respond to a subpoena, court order or other legal process. Finally, the Personal Information you provide to us may be transferred as an asset in connection with a merger or sale involving all or part of GoAntiques or as part of a corporate reorganization, stock sale or other change of control. 

**CHILDREN'S PRIVACY**

Only persons age 18 or older have permission to access our Service. Furthermore, our Site does not address anyone under the age of 13 (a "Child" or "Children"). 

We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from Children. If you are a parent or guardian and you learn that your Child or Children have provided us with Personal Information, please [**contact us**](mailto:goantiques@gemr.com). While we are not under any obligation to actively monitor our site for such information, if we become aware that we have collected Personal Information from a Child or Children under age 13 without verification of parental consent, we will do our best to remove that information from our servers in a timely manner. 

**SECURITY**

We employ reasonable security measures, including administrative, technical, and physical measures, to protect Personal Information from unauthorized access, loss, alteration, use or disclosure. However, Personal Information can never be 100% secure; third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications, and other users may abuse or misuse your personal information that they collect from the Site. Therefore although we work very hard to protect your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect that your personal information or private communications information will always remain private. You can help us to protect the Personal Information you provide to us by (i) not sharing your password or other account information with others, (ii) using a secure web browser, and (iii) frequently changing your password. 

**YOUR CHOICES**

You may update the information you provide by accessing your account and following the instructions for updating your information. You may opt-out of receiving certain types of communications from us ("Optional Communications"). However, you will not be able to opt-out of receiving other types of communications, such as service announcements and administrative messages, as these types of communications are necessary if you have an account with us. You may opt-out of receiving Optional Communications by following the instructions set forth in those communications or by accessing your account and following the instructions. If you have any questions regarding your ability to opt-out of receiving certain types of communications please contact us using our contact information set forth below in "Contact GoAntiques". Please note that removal of Personal Information from our database or "opting-out" will not stop marketing or advertising content that is ready to be mailed or is queued for transmission to you prior to the time when we can implement your request. 

**INFORMATION RETENTION POLICY**

We reserve the right to retain any Personal Information reasonably necessary to appropriately document our business activities and for archival and record retention purposes. We will store Personal Information for as long as reasonably necessary for the purposes described in this privacy policy. You may find out more details regarding this privacy policy by contacting us as provided below. 

**CONTACT US**

If you have questions regarding our Site, our services, the privacy policy or your privacy while accessing or using our Site, you can send a request with any further questions to us by e-mail at [**goantiques[at]gemr.com**](mailto:goantiques@gemr.com) or by mail at: 

GoAntiques, a Gemr Company 

230 Commerce Way. Suite 325 

Portsmouth, NH. 03801
